Register of the Sir Robert Hamilton Bruce Lockhart papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Incremental materials
  - Robin N. Bruce Lockhart file, 1904-2003
    - Sidney Reilly and the Russian Revolution file, 1918-2002
      - Kettle, Michael, 1967-1994 (Box-folder 10: 24)
      - Moscow visit and research, 1988 (Box-folder 10: 25)
      - Research and correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 10: 26)
      - Sources, 1918-2002
        - General, 1921-1997 (Box-folder 10: 27)
        - Charles, Pepita, 1925-1931 (Box-folder 10: 28)
        - Dukes, Paul, 1922-1990 (Box-folder 10: 29)
        - Foreign and Commonwealth Office, 1957-2002 (Box-folder 11: 1)
        - Lockhart, Robert Bruce and Sidney Reilly, 1918-1937 (Box-folder 11: 2)
        - Mallean, Jean, undated (Box-folder 11: 3)
          Mother of Robin N. Bruce Lockhart
        - Questionnaires, undated (Box-folder 11: 4)
        - Spears, Edward, 1920-1974 (Box-folder 11: 5)
    - Sidney Reilly documentary materials, 1904-1997 (Box-folder 11: 6-11)
      Includes writings by Robin Lockhart, research, and photographs
    - "Ring of Spies" file, 1975-1999
      - General, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 11: 12)
      - Greenberg, Michael, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 11: 13)
      - Henri, Ernest, 1985-1993 (Box-folder 11: 14)
        Also known as Semyon Rostotsky
      - Research visit to United States, 1985 (Box-folder 11: 15)
      - Traill, Vera, 1975-1999 (Box-folder 11: 16)
    - Moura Budberg Project file, 1918-1996
      - Alexander, Tania, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 11: 17)
      - Berbergva, Nina, 1989 (Box-folder 11: 18)
      - Budberg file, 1966-1996 (Box-folder 11: 19)
      - Copies of Budberg letters, 1918-1958, undated (Box-folder 11: 20)
    - Foreign and Commonwealth Office, 1972-2003 (Box-folder 11: 21)
    - Correspondence, 1944-1997 (Box-folder 11: 22)
  - Jan Masaryk/Czechoslovakia file
    Includes files of Robin Lockhart and Robert Lockart concerning Jan Masaryk.
    - General, 1954-1993 (Box-folder 12: 2)
    - Davenport, Marcia, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 12: 2)
    - Correspondence concerning book on Masaryk, 1991-1997 (Box-folder 12: 3)
    - Prague visits, 1991-1998 (Box-folder 12: 4)
      Includes description of medals awards to Robert Lockhart. See also Oversize materials, box 13.
    - Robert H. Bruce Lockhart files on Masaryk, 1941-1970 (Box-folder 12: 5)
      Includes photographs
    - Robert H. Bruce Lockhart outgoing correspondence, 1928-1949 (Box-folder 12: 6)
- Declassified British government records, 1918-1973
  Formerly security-classified records of the British government, released in full. Arranged chronologically by date of release by Hoover, thereunder chronologically by date of creation
  - 2010 release of records (see also Report to the British Foreign Office on a conversation with L. M. Karachan..., box 7, folder 5), 1918-1973; One folder (Box-folder 12: 7)
  - 2011 release of record, undated; One folder containing 1 item (Box-folder 12: 8)
  - 2017 release of records, 1918 (Reading room workstation)
- Oversize materials
  Contains a framed drawing and three medals.
  - Framed drawing, Dubrovnik, undated (Box 13)
  - Three medals, undated (Box 13)
    See Jan Masaryk/Czechoslovakia file (box 12, folder 4) for description of medals